Finding Aid for the Will Connell Papers LSC.0893
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Proofs and Negatives
  - Black & White lantern slide (1)
    - Glass negatives. (Box 148)
  - Bob Smith
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Brisacher - Wheeler - Qantas Air
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - Brock's
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Brock's - Diamonds
    - Glass negatives. (Box 142)
  - Brock's - Portraits
    - Glass negatives. (Box 142)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - Brock's - Vogue
    - Glass negatives. (Box 142)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
  - Brock's - Vogue (Including Notes)
    - Glass negatives. (Box 142)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Brock's 1
    - Glass negatives. (Box 136)
  - Brock's 1, October 1928
    - Glass negatives. (Box 139)
  - Brock's 10
    - Glass negatives. (Box 142)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
  - Brock's 2, December 1928
    - Glass negatives. (Box 139)
  - Brock's 3 - Silver Book
    - Glass negatives. (Box 139)
  - Brock's 4, March 1929
    - Glass negatives. (Box 140)
  - Brock's 5, June 1929
    - Glass negatives. (Box 140)
  - Brock's 6, October 1929
    - Glass negatives. (Box 140)
  - Brock's 7, Xmas 1929
    - Glass negatives. (Box 141)
  - Brock's 8, June 1930
    - Glass negatives. (Box 141)
    - Glass negatives. (Box 142)
  - Brock's 9, October 1930
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Brock's Interiors Tea Services
    - Glass negatives. (Box 142)
  - Brock's Newspaper, 1938
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Brock's, Xmas 1931
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Brownstein-Louis
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Business Week / EKCO Ware
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - California Fruit Growers
    - Glass negatives. (Box 126)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - California Fruit Growers Grapefruit Book
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - California Fruit Growers. Soda Fountain.
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - Carlos Vierra
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Carmen's Baptism
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Carter
    - Glass negatives. (Box 145)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Chrysons
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - City of Hope (Including 4 Colour Transparencies)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Coleman / Geissinger / Kinkel / Lola / Rocquemore
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Colour Lantern Slides
    - Glass negatives. (Box 148)
  - Conselman
    - Glass negatives. (Box 145)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Darwin Clark
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - David / Chinaman / Colonel Otto
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - Day and Nite
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Dick Williams
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Dorothy Danner
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Double X, U.S. & Miner
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - E.J. Strong
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Ed Colmans
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Edmundson 3-D Ply
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Electroweld
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 125)
  - Elizabeth Wood
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Erna Fergusson
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Eve O'Dell
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - EW - B.U.'s & BHG's broadside
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - EW - Biltmore Florists - Peke
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - EW - Carnation
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - EW - Congo
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - EW - Consumers Credit
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - EW - Conway Flowers
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - EW - Fluor
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - EW - Ghiradelli
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - EW - Interstate
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - EW - Laykin
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - EW - Lennen Lights
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - EW - Savabrush / Wayoff / Hydro Pura
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - EW - Shalk Chem, 1944
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - F.C. & B Hughes no.47-75
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - Falkenbury
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - F-C Loungers etc.
    - Safety negatives. (Box 125)
  - F-C Loungers, etc.
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - F-C Men of Distinction
    - Safety negatives. (Box 125)
  - F-C Mixed Bests [?]
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - F-C Tropicals & Hats
    - Safety negatives. (Box 125)
  - FC & B Hughes
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 132)
  - FC & B Hughes - Rejects
    - Safety negatives. (Box 132)
  - FC & B Papermate Camera
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - FC & B Rheem
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - FC & B Tesla Coil
    - Safety negatives. (Box 132)
  - Flower Guild
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Fluor
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 137)
  - Foreman Building
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
    - Glass negatives. (Box 131)
  - Fostvert - Frankenfield - Jos - Paget Fredericks
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Frank Taylor
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Franz Geritz [and Family]
    - Glass negatives. (Box 144)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Franz's Babies
    - Glass negatives. (Box 145)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - General Metals
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - George Harriman
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - George Hope / Nugent / Holzer / Bethel-Hodel
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Goldsmith
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - H & J Brock's, 1954
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - H.C. Vendome
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - H.S. Fassage
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - Hal S. - Practical Builder
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - Hal Stebbins
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Hancock Oil - Rejects
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Harry Carr / Charles Owen / Ramsey Oppenheim / Douglas McPhee
    - Glass negatives. (Box 144)
  - H-C Golf Caddy
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 125)
  - H-C Schalke, 1946
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - H-C Schalke, cash register, 1947
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - H-C Schalke, 1948
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - H-C Schalke, 1949
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - H-C U.S. Hardware & Paper Company
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - H-C United Motor Courts
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - Helen Seymour
    - Glass negatives. (Box 145)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Highland Syrup - Table Set-Up - Pickled Pear
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - HSB - Catalina
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - HSB - HOMIS
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - HSB - Natone
    - Glass negatives. (Box 128)
  - HSB - Plastic Compacts
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - Hunt Foods
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - Hunt Foods - Portraits
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Isabelle Blanchard
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - J. Rubels
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Jackman
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Jane Fones Job BTLO [?]
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - Jane Fones Job Color (Color Proofs)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - Jane Fones Job Color Alt
    - Safety negatives. (Box 132)
  - Jane Turner
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Jefferies Litho. (Including 15 colour Transparencies)
    - Glass negatives. (Box 126)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - Jim Hastings
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Jock Peters - Bachelors - Rewelling
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
  - Joe Hartman / Phil Meany / Ellis Fulton / McCarthy
    - Glass negatives. (Box 145)
  - John Henry Nash / Grabhorn Brothers / Valenti / Angelo / Bo Hon / Sanchez / MacCallish
    - Glass negatives. (Box 145)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - John Reardon - Caltex
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - John Thompson
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Kai Jorgenson
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Karl Struss
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Kenneth Adams
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Kitty Cameron
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Klemperer
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Ladd Haystead
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Ladd Haystead, 1949
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Lane - Wells
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - Lazurus
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Lee Jennings
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
  - Loker
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Lucy Stebbins
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Maclean
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - MacMillan / McCloud / Stace / Carl Smalley
    - Glass negatives. (Box 144)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - MacMillan O.I.
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Mannings
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Marion Harron
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Mariska
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Mathias
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Maxine
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - McCarty - National Seal
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - McCarty - Portraits
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - McCarty - Valves - Color
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - McClellan
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - McCulloch - Supercharger
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - McCulloch Motors - Heli Rejects
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - McCulloch Motors - Heli Rejects (Transparencies)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - McMenimen
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Mechanical Handling Bishop Goodyear
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Michael Griffith
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Millier
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Miscellaneous Portraits
    - Glass negatives. (Box 145)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Mission Dry
    - Safety negatives. (Box 131)
  - Models
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Mr. Babcock / Ruth Rankin / Peter Cook / Tommy Jackson / Karen / H. Grieves
    - Glass negatives. (Box 144)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Mr. Mann / McCarty's / Don Wilson / Helen Vinson
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Mrs. Gross
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Mrs. Robert Nivins
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Muller-Gosney (Note Only)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - National Auto - Portraits
    - Glass negatives. (Box 130)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
  - National Auto - Shop
    - Glass negatives. (Box 130)
  - National Auto Shop
    - Glass negatives. (Box 126)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - Nescafe
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Nescafe - Ann Rutherford
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Nescafe - Ann Rutherford (Transparencies)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Nescafe - Dick Powell
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Nescafe - Dick Powell (Transparencies)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Nescafe - E.G. Robinson
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Nescafe - E.G. Robinson (Transparencies)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Nescafe - Joan Davis
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Nescafe - Joan Davis (Transparencies)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Niven
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - North American
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - O'Dee / Gretchen O'Dell / Horton / Florence Atkinson
    - Glass negatives. (Box 144)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
  - Olds Instruments
    - Glass negatives. (Box 126)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - Orchids
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Paintings
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Paul G. Johnson (Including 2 Transparencies)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Paul Landacre
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Paul Sample - Portrait
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
  - Peter Behn
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Phylys Garan
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Pierce Brothers
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Plumb Tools
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Porter Blanchard
    - Glass negatives. (Box 136)
  - Porter Blanchard Flatware
    - Glass negatives. (Box 136)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 137)
  - Portrait - Specs - Goodyear - EW
    - Glass negatives. (Box 131)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
  - Portraits - Matches - Landscapes - Apples
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - Premier Paint
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Purex, 1944
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Pyrol
    - Glass negatives. (Box 131)
  - Radioplane
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Ralph Huesman / Ralph Hamer / Eddie George
    - Glass negatives. (Box 144)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - Ramo-Wooldridge
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Ray Morgan - Orchid
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Ray Winters
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - Ray Winters / Lee Jennings
    - Glass negatives. (Box 144)
  - Real - Union
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Reckless Asange
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Reese Taylor
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Reg Olds
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - Reg Olds. John Levy
    - Safety negatives. (Box 127)
  - Rheems
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 125)
  - Richard Richards
    - Glass negatives. (Box 131)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - Rieber - Columbia Aquagel
    - Glass negatives. (Box 136)
  - Roark Bradford
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Roy Durstine - Dietonic
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Roy Durstine - Hydro-Air
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Salon - Miscellaneous portraits
    - Glass negatives. (Box 145)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Sandburg-Johnson, Armitage, Charles Everit
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Schaeffer - Hammer
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Schalk, 1951 & 1952
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Schalk catalog, 1952 and 1948
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Serta Mattress
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Shackelford / Rodriguez / Ray Griffith / Tom Lebenthon
    - Glass negatives. (Box 144)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Sharp
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Sharp - Copies
    - Safety negatives. (Box 135)
  - Sheldon Parsons
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Simpson
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Sinclair Funeral
    - Safety negatives. (Box 134)
  - Sir Tobie Wright
    - Glass negatives. (Box 144)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - Sneeze Rejects
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Sonya Brown
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Southern California Aircraft
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Sprague, George
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 150)
  - Spud Johnson
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Sunjuis
    - Glass negatives. (Box 126)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
  - Sunkist, Single Col, 1937
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - Sunkist - Dates
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
  - Sunkist - Oranges
    - Glass negatives. (Box 131)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
  - Sunkist - Pattie [?]
    - Glass negatives. (Box 131)
  - Sunkist, September 29
    - Glass negatives. (Box 131)
  - Sunkist, - Pie - Lemons, September 29
    - Glass negatives. (Box 130, Box 131)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - Sunkist Cola
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - Sunkist Dental Ads
    - Glass negatives. (Box 131)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - Sunkist Juice
    - Glass negatives. (Box 130)
  - Sunkist Lemon & Soda, 1940
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - Sunkist Sneeze, 1944
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 128)
  - Sunkist Sneeze, 1945
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - Sunkist Sneezes
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - Sunset Conway
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)
  - Sven
    - Glass negatives. (Box 143)
  - Tasker
    - Glass negatives. (Box 145)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Tasker, 1948
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Ted Cook
    - Glass negatives. (Box 145)
  - The Diocese
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - The Mayers
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Theisen/ Faulkner / Landsdale / Bletsch / Ken Alexander
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Tickenor
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Toni Hughes
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Treanor
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 143)
  - Treviso / Brinn / Hal Stevens / McCarty
    - Glass negatives. (Box 144)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - Trujuis - Orange Juice
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 137)
  - U.S. 32
    - Glass negatives. (Box 145)
  - U.S. Motors
    - Glass negatives. (Box 130)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
  - United Piece Dye, Long Beach
    - Safety negatives. (Box 125)
  - Untitled
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - Untitled no.1-22
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - Untitled no.1-3
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - Untitled Negatives, (2 × 2 & 35mm.)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
    - Safety negatives. (Box 147)
  - Virginia Barnett
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Wayne Loel
    - Safety negatives. (Box 146)
  - Wessell's Ice Box
    - Glass negatives. (Box 131)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
    - Proofs. (Box 129)
  - Wilgus Gas Gauge
    - Glass negatives. (Box 126)
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 149)
  - Will Harrison
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Willy & Alice Corbin Henderson
    - Nitrate negatives. (Box 151)
  - Y & R - Cole of California
    - Safety negatives. (Box 133)
  - Y & R - Ohio Match
    - Safety negatives. (Box 138)